Guide to the Nate Brown Western Sound Archive Collection ARS.0124
Archive of Recorded Sound
- 394. Prague Festival No.1, 1964-05; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 5)
- 395. Prague Festival No.2, 1964-05; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 5)
- 397. Prague Festival No.4, 1964-05; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 5)
- 398. Prague Festival No.5, 1964-05; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 5)
- 404. Szell, Cleveland Orchestra. Cassella; Respighi; Brahms, 1961-10-05; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 5)
- 405. Szell, Cleveland Orchestra. Haydn; Debussy; Albeniz; Strauss; Louis Lane Interview, 1960-1964; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 5)
- 406. Szell, Cleveland Orchestra. Beethoven, Symphony No. 4 1964; Shaw, Cleveland Orchestra. Walton, Belshazzar's Feast 1961; Szell Discusses Toscanini 1/1965, 1961-1965; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 5)
- 413. Solti, London Symphony Orchestra. United Nations Concert, TV, 1964-10-24; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 6)
- 415. Szell, Cleveland Orchestra. Tchaikovsky, Symphony No.4; Schumann, Symphony No.3; Strauss, Emperor Waltz, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 6)
- 416. Steinberg, New York Philharmonic, U.S. Military Band, Berlioz; Jacques Barzun Discussion, 1964-12; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 6)
- 416 (2). Szell, Cleveland Orchestra. Schumann; Szell, Lane Discussions, 1961-1962; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 6)
- 418. Szell, Cleveland Orchestra. Wagner; Tchaikovsky; Verdi; Ravel, 1962-1963; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 6)
- 424. Ormandy, Philadelphia Orchestra, Gilels. Thorne; Chopin; Schumann, 1964-11; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 6)
- 426. Net Television Concerts No.4. Sargent, Royal Philharmonic Orchestra. Elgar; Williams; Britten. Symphony Hall, Boston 10/6/63; Stockhausen, Buffalo Philharmonic. Stockhausen, Momente. American Premiere 3/1/64, 1963-1964; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 6)
- 427. Net Television Concerts No.5. Rudolf, Cincinnati Symphony 4/10/64; Sargent, Royal Philharmonic Orchestra 10/6/63, 1963-1964; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 6)
- 434. Steinberg, Schippers, New York Philharmonic, 1964-1965; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 6)
- 441. Stokowski, Kimio Eto; Ormandy, Philadelphia Orchestra, Menuhin, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 6)
- 443. Ormandy, Philadelphia Orchestra, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 6)
- 451. Philadelphia Orchestra; Hollywood Bowl, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 6)
- 458. Salzburg Festival. Mehta, Berlin Philharmonic, 1964.; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 6)
- 464. Krips, Anders, San Francisco Symphony, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 6)
- 465. Krips, San Francisco Symphony. February- March, 1965; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 6)
- 466. Krips, San Francisco Symphony, 1965-01-08; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 6)
- 489. Fung No.4. Mehta. Apostel, Piano Concerto; Wermser, Strauss as Conductor; Bohm. Wagner, Meistersinger Act I, Bayreuth; I.J. Fung Talk, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 6)
- 491. Fung No.6. Furtwangler Program; Britten. Purcell 12/20/64; Mozart, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 6)
- 494. Herrmann, CBS Symphony 10/20/49. Raff, Symphony No.3 in F, Op. 153 WDRC-FM, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 6)
- 497. Art Museum Concert, KPFK [Los Angeles County Museum opening]; Wallenstein, Congress of Strings, AFM, Michigan State University, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 6)
- 555. Net Television Concerts. Jorda, San Francisco Symphony 5/16/63; Steinberg, Pittsburgh Symphony 4/26/63, 1963; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 6)
- 567. KPFK. Roy Harris, Symphony no.10. Premiere, UCLA 4/14/65; Virgil Thomson, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 6)
- 568. WFLN. Ormandy, Philadelphia Orchestra. March, April, 1965; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 6)
- 569. WFLN, Ormandy, Philadelphia Orchestra, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 6)
- 571. Samuel, Oakland Symphony. Milhaud, Beethoven, Ravel, Hindemith, Mozart, Myrow; Krips, San Francisco Symphony. Hindemith, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 6)
- 579. Van Beinum, Amsterdam Concertgebouw; Haitink, Nederland Orchestra, Orof; Perrault, CBC Orchestra, Montreal; Hurst, BBC Northern Orchestra and Chorus; Haitink, Amsterdam Concertgebouw; Italian Music Hall, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 6)
- 581. Bellini, Norma pt. 1 [also numbered 1464, with insert of WAKR-FM 9/14/69 broadcast], 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 6)
- 583. Respighi, La Fiamma 1; Mengelberg. Concertgebouw Orchestra. Kodaly, Peacock Variations 11/23/1939; Cassado. Pfitzner, Cello Concerto in G, Op. 42 12/12/40 [also numbered 1367], 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 6)
- 601. Stoessel, Juilliard School of Music Orchestra, Ajemian. Khatchaturian, Piano Concerto 1943; Endres String Quartet, Michaels. Hitzacker Summer Festival 1964, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 6)
- 605. Stokowski, New York Philharmonic, Landowska. Poulenc 1949; Schnabel. Mozart, Sonata in B-flat K.333 1943, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 6)
- 609. Hollywood Bowl. Previn, Los Angeles Philharmonic, Pennario, 1965-07-06; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 6)
- 620. Boskousky, Vienna Philharmonic. Strauss. New Year's Day Concert, BBC TV, 1965; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 6)
- 621. BBC Recordings. Giulini Talking, TV 1/5/65; Dorati, BBCSO. Falla 1/5/65; Scheuricht, LSO. Haydn. 1/9/65; Davis, LSO. Weber 9/7/63; Brahms, Mozart 1/4/65, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 6)
- 631. Szell, Amsterdam Concertgebouw. Radio Nederland. Ricciotti, Sibelius, 1964; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 6)
- 632. Pfitzner Concert. Reichert, Westphalische Symphoniker, 1965-06; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 6)
- 636. Paganini, 3 Quartets for Guitar and Strings. RAI Tapes 32,33,34; RAI Orchestra. Dittersdorf, 3 Symphonies; Bream, Carmirelli Quartet. Haydn, Quartet in D for Guitar and Strings. BBC, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 6)
- 639. Rozhdestvensky, Leningrad Symphony Orchestra. 1960 Edinburgh Festival. Britten, Shostakovich; BBC. Miaskovsky, Tchaikovsky, Prokokiev, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 6)
- 652. Salzburg Festival, 1964; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 7)
- 668. Music From Germany; RAI, Monteverdi; Radio Philharmonic; Radio Nederland; Music From Belgium, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 7)
- 669. Concerts From BBC. Basil Cameron, Conductor, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 7)
- 691. Besancon Festival. Contemporary Chamber Music Concert, 1964; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 7)
- 692. Goldberg, Netherlands Chamber Orchestra. Haydn, Mozart. Radio Netherlands Concert No.57, 64-65 Season, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 31)
- 693. Rosbaud Conducts Modern Music No.1, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 7)
- 694. Rosbaud Conducts Modern Music No.2, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 7)
- 695. Dennis Brain Program. Aldeburgh Festival 1955; Stravinsky/Webern Program. Aldeburgh 1961, BBC, 1955-1961; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 7)
- 696. Samuel, Oakland Symphony, Stern. Dvorak. KKHI, 1965-02; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 7)
- 697. Pittsburgh International Contemporary Music Festival, 1955; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 7)
- 698. Beethoven Quartet, Shostakovich, String Quartets. Sibelius Festival, 1959; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 7)
- 700. Donaueschingen Festival. All Stravinsky Program, 1962; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 7)
- 703. Sibelius Festival, 1965; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 7)
- 718. Ehrling, Philadelphia Orchestra, 1964; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 7)
- 719. Sibelius Tribute. A Symphony for Finland, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 7)
- 720. Sawallish, Vienna Philharmonic. Schmidt, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 7)
- 722. Fung No.11. Davis, London Symphony, Serkin. Brahms, Piano Concerto No.1, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 7)
- 723. Fung No.12. Dorati, BBC Symphony. Stravinsky; Del Mar, BBC Scottish Orchestra, Rostal. Reger, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 7)
- 749. Ormandy, Philadelphia Orchestra, Menuhin. Beethoven, Violin Concerto, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 7)
- 774. Stokowski, Boston Symphony; Ormandy, Philadelphia Orchestra, 1965; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 7)
- 795. Minneapolis Symphony broadcast [clipping enclosed], 1965-12-30; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 7)
- 796. Minneapolis Symphony broadcast [clipping enclosed], 1966-01-14; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 7)
- 804. Fung No.15. Kempe, BBC Symphony. Bruckner 6/5/65; Boult, London Philharmonic, Menuhin. Elgar 2/2/65; Kempe, BBC Symphony. Beethoven 6/5/65; Bertini, Bath Festival Orchestra, Menuhin. Williamson 6/15/65, 1965; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 7)
- 805. Fung No.16. Klemperer, New Philharmonia, Menuhin. Berlioz; Beethoven, 1966-01-30; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 7)
- 806. Fung No.17. Boult, LSO. Williams; Tedesco; Brahms 5/5/65; Sargent, LPO, Oistrakh. Ysaye 2/26/61; Segovia, RFH 5/5/65, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 7)
- 888. Fung No.19. Boult, LPO, Menuhin 2/2/65; Davis, LSO 2/1/65; Klemperer, Concertgebouw 7/19/61, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 7)
- 810. Fung No.21. Dorati, BBC Symphony 1/12/65; Kubelik, Rome Symphony 12/31/65; IJF Talking 2/16/66, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 7)
- 812. Fung No.23. Dorati, BBC Symphony. Williams 5/16/65; Szell, Cleveland Symphony. Barber 6/21/65; Schurich, Hague Residencie Orchestra. Mozart; [illeg.], 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 7)
- 813. Fung No.24. [illeg.] 5/9/65; Dorati, BBC Symphony. Blachner, Tipett 5/9/65; Klemperer, New Philharmonia. Beethoven 2/20/66, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 7)
- 821. Mitropoulos, New York Philharmonic. Haydn; Brahms, 1950-01-01; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 7)
- 822. Walter, New York Philharmonic, 1950-02-05; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 7)
- 830. Snook No.1. All Stokowski, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 7)
- 832. Snook No.3. Bachhaus and Stokowski, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 7)
- 833. Snook No.4. Landowska, Frick Museum Recitals 1950, 1951, 1954, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 31)
- 834. Snooks No.5. New York Philharmonic, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 7)
- 835A. Miaskovsky, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 7)
- 861. Rodzinsky, NY Philharmonic. Schuman. CBS; Schmidt-Isserstedt, SF Symphony. Lutoslawski 2/11/66, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 31)
- 873. Szell, Cleveland Orchestra. Bruckner 1/27/66; Goldberg, Netherlands Chamber Orchestra. Radio Nederland, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 7)
- 876. De Sabata, New York Philharmonic, Arrau. Schumann; Beethoven, 1951-03-18; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 7)
- 878. Hollywood Bowl Concert pt.1. Craft, Stravinsky, Los Angeles Philharmonic, 1966-07-05; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 8)
- 879. Hollywood Bowl Concert pt.2. Craft, Stravinsky, Los Angeles Philharmonic, 1966-07-05; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 8)
- 881. Stokowski, Cleveland Symphony [D-98 also on box], 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 8)
- 886. Bath Festival, Menuhin. Mozart 6/22/66; Lord, LSO, Stern. Bach 6/23/66; LSO, Stern. Bach, Haydn 4/23/66, 1966; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 8)
- 893. Bolet, RPO. Spanish Music; Schutz, Story of the Birth of Jesus Christ [BBC TS discs 104170-3], 1959; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 8)
- 895. Geraint Jones Orchestra. Bach, Mozart [BBC 107147/8]; Aldeburgh Festival. Berg Program, 1961; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 8)
- 896. All Chopin Recital by Rubinstein. BBC, 1960; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 8)
- 902. Netherlands String Quartet. UC Berkeley, 1966-07-29; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 8)
- 909. Cheltenham Festival; Del Mar, RPO, Oistrakh. BBC, 1960; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 8)
- 910. Radio Nederland Transcriptions [1213 also on box], 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 8)
- 911. Danon, Zagreb Philharmonic, Rostropovitch. Britten, Khatchaturian, 1965-05-12; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 8)
- 915. Rosbaud Conducts Modern Music. Penderecki; Stockhausen; Berio. SWF Transcription Service, Baden-Baden, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 8)
- 916. La Salle Quartet, Zagreb Festival, 1965; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 8)
- 917. Rowicki, Polish National Philharmonic. Webern; Schoenberg; Szymanowski. Warsaw Autumn Festival, 1962-11-08; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 8)
- 918. Josef Hofmann, 1943-1947; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 8)
- 919. Wallenstein, Los Angeles Philharmonic, Schnabel, 1945-03-04; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 8)
- 921. Lane, Cleveland Orchestra, 1966-11-20; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 8)
- 929. Monteux, San Francisco Symphony, Ricci 12/23/51, 2/3/52, 3/30/52; Heifetz. Debussy 2/3/52; Mitropoulos, NY Philharmonic 2/14/54, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 8)
- 930. Monteux, San Francisco Symphony, 1950-1956; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 8)
- 945. Maderna, Liege Symphony Orchestra. Bartok. Belgian Radio-TV tape; Kempe, Berlin Philharmonic. Haydn. Salzburg Festival 1962, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 8)
- 947. Craft, Stravinsky, Israeli Philharmonic, Zeitlin. Israel Festival; Demus, etc. Schubert. Vienna Festival, 1962; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 8)
- 948. Amadeus Quartet, Saltzmann. Schumann. Israel Festival; Robinson, BBC Symphony. Clementi, 1962; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 8)
- 952. Kempe, Berlin Philharmonic, Magaloff. Salzburg Festival 1962; Paumgartner, Salzburg Mozarteum Orchestra; Kempe, Berlin Philharmonic, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 8)
- 953. Munch, Chicago Symphony, Vronsky, Babin. Ravinia Festival, 1966-07-02; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 8)
- 960. San Francisco Symphony, Casadesus. KKHI 12/16/66; Rosbaud, Munich Radio Orchestra [Polydor]; Lehmann, Berlin Philharmonic [DGG], 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 8)
- 963. Harris, Concerto For Piano and Strings. World Premiere Broadcast; Villa-Lobos, Hollywood Bowl Orchestra, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 8)
- 964. Klemperer, LA Philharmonic. Hollywood Bowl Special Summer Concert; Walter, NBC, Szigeti, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 8)
- 965. Monteux, San Francisco Symphony. Standard Hour, 1947-1951; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 8)
- 967. NBC Symphony Orchestra, 1951; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 8)
- 968. Monteux, Boston Symphony Orchestra. Schumann; Mitropoulos, NY Philharmonic 4/26/53, 4/25/54, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 8)
- 971. Walter, NY Philharmonic, Horowitz, 1948-04-11; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 8)
- 973. Klemperer, Philadelphia Orchestra. WQXR rebroadcast 5/28/66; Szell, Cleveland Orchestra, Serkin WQXR 5/5/66, 1966; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 8)
- 974. Walter, NY Philharmonic. Mahler, Symphony No.1; Dukas, Sorceror's Apprentice. AFRS, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 8)
- 979. Furtwangler, La Scala Orchestra and Chorus. Gluck, Orfeo 1, 1950; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 8)
- 980. Furtwangler, La Scala Orchestra and Chorus. Gluck, Orfeo 2. 1950; Paumgartner, Vienna Philharmonic, Tissu-Vallentin. Salzburg Festival 1953; Waxman, LA Music Festival. Debussy 1, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 8)
- 981. Goldberg, Boston Symphony, Dwyer. Berkshire Festival. All Bach Program, 1966; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 8)
- 982. Walter, NY Philharmonic. Brahms [crossed out], 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 8)
- 983. Walter, NY Philharmonic, 1953-12-20; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 9)
- 987. Ives. Bernstein, NY Philharmonic 2/25/51; Mullen 9/24/50; Music on the Roof 5/13/51, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 9)
- 992. Walter, NY Philharmonic, 1948-01-25; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 9)
- 994. Monteux, SF Symphony, Spivakovsky, 1952-01-13; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 9)
- 996. Besancon Festival. Kucherov, USSR Philharmonic, 1966; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 9)
- 999. Monteux, SF Symphony, Standard Hour March 9, March 30, 1952-03; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 9)
- 1003. Prague Spring Festival, 1966; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 9)
- 1006. Walter, New York Philharmonic. Beethoven, Mozart, Brahms, 1954-11-28; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 31)
- 1007. Walter, NY Philharmonic. Rehearsing and Recording Brahms 2nd; Berlioz, 1954-11-21; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 9)
- 1010. Walter, NY Philharmonic, 1954-01-17; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 9)
- 1011. De Sabata, NY Philharmonic, 1950-03-19; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 9)
- 1012. De Sabata, New York Philharmonic March 5, March 25, 1950-03; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 9)
- 1118. Samuel, Oakland Symphony, Arrau. Debussy, Felciano, Chopin. 1966/67 Season, Concert No.4, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 31)
- 1167. Ormandy, Philadelphia Orchestra, Goldberg. Brahms, Violin Concerto in D Major; Boulez, Cleveland Orchestra. Haydn, Sinfonia Concertante, Op.84 11/19/67; Beecham, BBC Symphony. Berlioz, King Lear 12/54, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 31)
- 1020. Munch, Chicago Symphony, Henriot-Schweitzer. Ravinia Festival WFMT, 1966-07-05; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 9)
- 1021. BBC/Fung. Szell, Cleveland Orchestra 4/1/66; Dorati, BBCSO 4/3/66, 4/4/66, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 9)
- 1022. BBC/Fung. Petrassi, BBC Northern Orchestra 6/30/66; Boulton, BBC Northern Singers and Orchestra 7/4/66, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 9)
- 1023. BBC/Fung. Gibson, Scottish National Orchestra 8/28/66; Band of HM Royal Marines 4/12/66; Boult, Halle Orchestra, Williamson, 1966; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 9)
- 1024. BBC/Fung. Kosler, Prague Symphony Orchestra 2/12/67; Davis, LSO, Rostropovich 10/5/66, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 9)
- 1033. San Francisco Symphony. Standard Hour; NBC Concert Orchestra, 1954-1955; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 9)
- 1037. Rosbaud, BBC Symphony 3/22/61; Kodaly, BBC Symphony 10/2/60; Davis, LSO 7/8/64 [etc.], 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 9)
- 1042. Horowitz, Carnegie Hall, 1966-11-27; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 9)
- 1044. Bruno Walter Program of Commentaries, Reminiscences and Eulogies, CBC [crossed out], 1963; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 9)
- 1045. Sargent, LPO, Oistrakhs. Royal Albert Hall p.2, 1961; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 9)
- 1045. Sargent, LPO, Oistrakhs. Royal Albert Hall p.1, 1961; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 9)
- 1049. Pritchard, RPO. 14th Edinburgh Festival, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 9)
- 1050. Aldeburgh Festival. Britten, LSO, 1961; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 9)
- 1051. Rozhdestvensky, Philharmonia. 16th Edinburgh Festival, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 9)
- 1055A. Mitropoulos, NY Philharmonic. January 1, January 23, 1960-01; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 9)
- 1055B. Mitropoulos, NY Philharmonic. KNX, 1960-01-03; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 9)
- 1056. Scherchen, Philadelphia Orchestra 11/22/64; Leinsdorf, BPO 9/24/66, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 9)
- 1057. Ormandy, Philadelphia Orchestra, Gueden, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 9)
- 1058. Copland, Cleveland Orchestra, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 9)
- 1059. Leinsdorf, BPO, Lateiner 1/6/67; Shaw, Cleveland Symphony, Boatwright 3/23/67, 1967; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 9)
- 1060. Pretre, Cleveland Orchestra, 1967-04-02; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 9)
- 1080. Giulini, Chicago Symphony. All Mozart, 1967-03-02; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 9)
- 1089. Dennis Brain, Horn, 1956-1957; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 9)
- 1091. Vienna Philharmonic, Della Casa. Bach, Strauss. Salzburg Festival 1958; Jalas, Finlandia Orchestra. Madetoja 10/3/59; Fladmoe, Beigen Harmonien Orchestra, Bjoner; Goldberg, Netherlands Chamber Orchestra [possibly switched reels with 2011], 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 32)
- 1097. Giulini, Chicago Symphony, Rubenstein 3/67; Martinon, Chicago Symphony, Rostropovich 1966, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 9)
- 1101. Kubelik, Chicago Symphony, Menuhin, 1966-12-15; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 9)
- 1103. Goehr, LSO 1960; Maderna, BBC Symphony 1959; Prausnitz, New Philharmonia 5/67, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 9)
- 1114A. Scherchen, RAI; Beecham, University of Illinois Orchestra 4/25/56; Scherchen, A. Scarlatti Orchestra of RAI, Laszlo, Gazzelloni, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 10)
- 1117. Kertesz, Philadelphia Orchestra. 1966-67 Season, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 10)
- 1120. Salzburg Festival. Bohm, VPO; Kempe, BPO, 1962; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 10)
- 1121. Dupre, Spoleto Festival 1966; Szell, Cleveland Orchestra 1967, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 10)
- 1122. Steinberg, New York Philharmonic, Ashkenazy 4/15/67; Rich Interviews Steinberg about Hindemith; Mehta, Montreal Symphony, Ashkenazy 1966 [CBC RM-164], 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 10)
- 1123. Steinberg, NY Philharmonic. Hindemith 4/15/67; Rosbaud, RAI (Rome); Freccia, RAI (Turin), Scardina; Previtali, Rai (Rome), 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 10)
- 1124. Boulez, BBC Symphony, Menuhin. Bath Festival, 1967; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 10)
- 1132. Kubelik, Chicago Symphony, 1966-12-22; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 10)
- 1137. Kempe, Royal Philharmonic, Richter-Haaser. Edinburgh Festival 1959; Kondrashin, Moscow Philharmonic, Ashkenazy. BBC; Reiner, Chicago Symphony, Anda 3/20/58, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 10)
- 1138. Busch, Danish Radio Symphony Orchestra, 1950-07-09; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 10)
- 1141. Walter, Vienna Philharmonic, Schwartzkopf 5/29/60; Walter, Swedish Radio Orchestra 9/8/50, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 10)
- 1141A. Michelangeli Studio Recital, BBC, 1959; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 10)
- 1150. Hoffnung Festival 1956 [etc.], 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 10)
- 1164. Rosbaud, Scherchen. Modern Music, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 10)
- 1168. Rosbaud, Bergman, Grabingen, Seiler. Bartok; Haskil, Rosabaud, SWR. Hindemith, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 10)
- 1173. Havergal Brian 2, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 10)
- 1174. Havergal Brian 1, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 10)
- 1175A. Reiner, NBC Symphony Orchestra, 1950-10-23; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 10)
- 1175. Reiner, NBC Symphony, 1950-10-23; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 10)
- 1176. Donati, RPO. Kodaly, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 10)
- 1178. Walter, Amsterdam Concertgebouw, Horowitz 2/20/36; Michelangeli, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 10)
- 1181. Furtwangler, Concertgebouw, 1950-07-13; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 10)
- 1190. Boulez, BBCSO, 1967; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 10)
- 1194. Quinet, Liege Symphony [Decca, Belgium 473.395], 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 10)
- 1204. Katims, Seattle Symphony [Private Record] 1964; Busch, NY Philharmonic 2/9/42 [Fritz Busch Society]; Furtwangler, Vienna Philharmonic 1944, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 10)
- 1208. Schmidt-Isserstedt, Chicago Symphony, 1968-04-18; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 10)
- 1209. Ansermet, Chicago Symphony, 1968-01-25; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 10)
- 1212. Samuel, Oakland Chamber Orchestra. 66-67 Season Program II; Malcolm, Philharmonia, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 10)
- 1215. Joseph Szigeti, Violin. Mozart Violin/Piano Sonatas Vol.1. Sub-masters from Vanguard, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 10)
- 1216. Michelangeli, Carnegie Hall Recital, 1966-01-21; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 31)
- 1217. Michelangeli, Carnegie Hall Recital, 1967-02-24; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 31)
- 1220. Samuel, Oakland Symphony. Mozart; Berg; Tchaikovsky, 1967-11; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 10)
- 1221. Samuel, Oakland Symphony. Beethoven; Bartok; Schumann, 1967-10; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 10)
- 1222. Samuel, Oakland Symphony, Goldberg, Nelsova, 1967-12; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 31)
- 1223. Craft, Oakland Symphony, Chorus. Stravinsky, 1968-02; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 10)
- 1235A. Furtwangler, VPO. Salzburg, 1951-08; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 10)
- 1235. Furtwangler, VPO. Bruckner. Salzburg Festival, 1951-08; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 10)
- 1241. Hermann, CBS Symphony. Ives, 1947-09-14; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 10)
- 1242. Strauss, Vienna State Opera Orchestra 2/15/42; Mitropoulos, NY Philharmonic, Schola Cantorum, Tozzi 5/12/57, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 10)
- 1243. Landowska. Mozart, Piano Sonata in F, K.332 [unissued Pathe-Marconi test], 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 11)
- 1244. Mitropoulos, NY Philharmonic, 1953-10-25; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 11)
- 1250. Mengelberg, Concertgebouw. Beethoven c.1942; Furtwangler, Berlin Philharmonic. Beethoven; Kubelik, Bavarian Radio Symphony Orchestra. Berlin Festival 1963, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 11)
- 1251. Reiner, Chicago Symphony, 1958-02-06; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 11)
- 1253. Rossi, RAI (Turin); Waldhaus, Brno Philharmonic, Blumenthal; Mengelberg, Concertgebouw, Sauer 1938; Colonna, Scarlatti Orchestra, D'Onorrio, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 11)
- 1255. Stokowski, American Symphony Orchestra, 1968-05-20; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 11)
- 1260. Boult, LPO; Kempe, BBCSO; Boehm, Czech Philharmonic. Salzburg Festival 1967; Ormandy, LSO; Boehm, Vienna Philharmonic. Vienna Festival 1967; Mravinsky, Leningrad Philharmonic. Prague Festival 1967, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 11)
- 1263. Paredi, RAI (Rome); Mehta, Beromunster Radio Orchestra, Barenboim, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 11)
- 1269. Furtwangler, 1950-1954; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 11)
- 1270. Furtwangler, RAI (Turin), De Vito, 1952-03; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 11)
- 1271. Michelangeli, Teatro Della Pergola acetates, 1952-02-12; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 11)